i amscls: AMS document classes for LaTeX
i amsfonts: TeX fonts from the American Mathematical Society
i amsmath: AMS mathematical facilities for LaTeX
i atbegshi: Execute stuff at \shipout time
i attachfile: Attach arbitrary files to a PDF document
i atveryend: Hooks at the very end of a document
i auxhook: Hooks for auxiliary files
i babel: Multilingual support for LaTeX, LuaLaTeX, XeLaTeX, and Plain TeX
i babel-english: Babel support for English
i bibtex: Process bibliographies (bib files) for LaTeX or other formats
i bibtex.windows: windows files of bibtex
i bigintcalc: Integer calculations on very large numbers
i bitset: Handle bit-vector datatype
i booktabs: Publication quality tables in LaTeX
i caption: Customising captions in floating environments
i cm: Computer Modern fonts
i ctablestack: Catcode table stable support
i dehyph: German hyphenation patterns for traditional orthography
i dvipdfmx: An extended version of dvipdfm
i dvipdfmx.windows: windows files of dvipdfmx
i dvips: A DVI to PostScript driver
i dvips.windows: windows files of dvips
i ec: Computer modern fonts in T1 and TS1 encodings
i embedfile: Embed files into PDF
i enumitem: Control layout of itemize, enumerate, description
i epstopdf-pkg: Call epstopdf "on the fly"
i etex: An extended version of TeX, from the NTS project
i etexcmds: Avoid name clashes with e-TeX commands
i etoolbox: e-TeX tools for LaTeX
i euenc: Unicode font encoding definitions for XeTeX
i everyshi: Take action at every \shipout
i fancyhdr: Extensive control of page headers and footers in LaTeX2e
i fancyvrb: Sophisticated verbatim text
i filehook: Hooks for input files
i firstaid: First aid for external LaTeX files and packages that need updating
i float: Improved interface for floating objects
i fontawesome: Font containing web-related icons
i fontspec: Advanced font selection in XeLaTeX and LuaLaTeX
i framed: Framed or shaded regions that can break across pages
i geometry: Flexible and complete interface to document dimensions
i gettitlestring: Clean up title references
i glyphlist: Adobe Glyph List and TeX extensions
i graphics: The LaTeX standard graphics bundle
i graphics-cfg: Sample configuration files for LaTeX color and graphics
i graphics-def: Colour and graphics option files
i helvetic: URW 'Base 35' font pack for LaTeX
i hycolor: Implements colour for packages hyperref and bookmark
i hyperref: Extensive support for hypertext in LaTeX
i hyph-utf8: Hyphenation patterns expressed in UTF-8
i hyphen-base: core hyphenation support files
i iftex: Am I running under pdfTeX, XeTeX or LuaTeX?
i inconsolata: A monospaced font, with support files for use with TeX
i infwarerr: Complete set of information/warning/error message macros
i intcalc: Expandable arithmetic operations with integers
i knuth-lib: Core TeX and Metafont sources from Knuth
i kpathsea: Path searching library for TeX-related files
i kpathsea.windows: windows files of kpathsea
i kvdefinekeys: Define keys for use in the kvsetkeys package
i kvoptions: Key value format for package options
i kvsetkeys: Key value parser with default handler support
i l3backend: LaTeX3 backend drivers
i l3kernel: LaTeX3 programming conventions
i l3packages: High-level LaTeX3 concepts
i latex: A TeX macro package that defines LaTeX
i latex-amsmath-dev: Development pre-release of the LaTeX amsmath bundle
i latex-bin: LaTeX executables and man pages
i latex-bin.windows: windows files of latex-bin
i latex-fonts: A collection of fonts used in LaTeX distributions
i latex-tools-dev: Development pre-release of the LaTeX tools bundle
i latexconfig: configuration files for LaTeX-related formats
i latexmk: Fully automated LaTeX document generation
i latexmk.windows: windows files of latexmk
i letltxmacro: Let assignment for LaTeX macros
i lm: Latin modern fonts in outline formats
i lm-math: OpenType maths fonts for Latin Modern
i ltxcmds: Some LaTeX kernel commands for general use
i lua-alt-getopt: Process application arguments the same way as getopt_long
i lua-uni-algos: Unicode algorithms for LuaTeX
i luahbtex: LuaTeX with HarfBuzz library for glyph shaping
i luahbtex.windows: windows files of luahbtex
i lualatex-math: Fixes for mathematics-related LuaLaTeX issues
i lualibs: Additional Lua functions for LuaTeX macro programmers
i luaotfload: OpenType 'loader' for Plain TeX and LaTeX
i luaotfload.windows: windows files of luaotfload
i luatex: The LuaTeX engine
i luatex.windows: windows files of luatex
i luatexbase: Basic resource management for LuaTeX code
i marvosym: Martin Vogel's Symbols (marvosym) font
i mdwtools: Miscellaneous tools by Mark Wooding
i metafont: A system for specifying fonts
i metafont.windows: windows files of metafont
i mfware: Supporting tools for use with Metafont
i mfware.windows: windows files of mfware
i modes: A collection of Metafont mode_def's
i natbib: Flexible bibliography support
i pdfescape: Implements pdfTeX's escape features using TeX or e-TeX
i pdftex: A TeX extension for direct creation of PDF
i pdftex.windows: windows files of pdftex
i pdftexcmds: LuaTeX support for pdfTeX utility functions
i plain: The Plain TeX format
i psnfss: Font support for common PostScript fonts
i refcount: Counter operations with label references
i rerunfilecheck: Checksum based rerun checks on auxiliary files
i scheme-infraonly: infrastructure-only scheme (no TeX at all)
i selnolig: Selectively disable typographic ligatures
i setspace: Set space between lines
i stringenc: Converting a string between different encodings
i symbol: URW 'Base 35' font pack for LaTeX
i tex: A sophisticated typesetting engine
i tex-ini-files: Model TeX format creation files
i tex.windows: windows files of tex
i texlive-scripts: TeX Live infrastructure programs
i texlive-scripts.windows: windows files of texlive-scripts
i texlive.infra: basic TeX Live infrastructure
i texlive.infra.windows: windows files of texlive.infra
i times: URW 'Base 35' font pack for LaTeX
i tipa: Fonts and macros for IPA phonetics characters
i titlesec: Select alternative section titles
i tlgs.windows: Freely available PostScript interpreter
i tlperl.windows: internal Perl for Windows
i tools: The LaTeX standard tools bundle
i ulem: Package for underlining
i unicode-data: Unicode data and loaders for TeX
i unicode-math: Unicode mathematics support for XeTeX and LuaTeX
i uniquecounter: Provides unlimited unique counter
i url: Verbatim with URL-sensitive line breaks
i xcolor: Driver-independent color extensions for LaTeX and pdfLaTeX
i xetex: An extended variant of TeX for use with Unicode sources
i xetex.windows: windows files of xetex
i xetexconfig: crop.cfg for XeLaTeX
i xkeyval: Extension of the keyval package
i xunicode: Generate Unicode characters from accented glyphs
i zapfding: URW 'Base 35' font pack for LaTeX
